https://valsurf.com/privacy-policy/

• HOLIDAY ORDERS -  We aim for speedy order processing, however, we cannot assure December 24th delivery for orders placed after December 16th.  In a pinch? Try a Gift Card.
Skip to content
Skip to search
Skip to footer
×
Search
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been created to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app? When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information? We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey or enter information on our site.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
• To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
• To improve our website in order to better serve you.
• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
• To quickly process your transactions.
• To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products
• To follow up with you after correspondence (email or phone inquiries)
How do we protect your information? Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of people who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
×
×
OK
Categories
2021 Step On
men
All men
footwear
Independent Truck Co.
Email Address:
Password:
Forgot your password?
Create Account
Gift Certificates
